xcoins.io 2018-07-04

# Privacy | xCoins.io

xCoins (referred to herein as "we", "our" or "the company") considers the privacy of our customers as well as visitors to our website to be extremely important. This Privacy Policy describes in detail the types of personal information collected and recorded on our website and how we use it.

### INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT

We may collect information from you when you visit our website, fill out a form on our website, subscribe to any newsletters or blogs we may offer, and when you apply for a loan through xCoins. We may use this information in any one or more of the following ways:

  1. To improve customer service, as your information helps us to more effectively respond to your service requests and support needs.
  2. To process transactions for you (i.e., loans) or help your online activities.
  3. To send periodic emails that may contain information about xCoins, the products and services we offer, and other information that you may find useful. The emails may also be used to send you information and updates about your loan transaction.
  4. To assist you in locating other companies capable of delivering products, services or information in which you may have an interest.

#### The information we may collect could consist of any of the following:

This could consist of your name, email address, mailing address or a phone number that you enter on our website. (Of course, you are free to visit our website without entering any of that information.) In connection with a loan application or transaction, you might enter additional information, which could include your social security number, your financial information, a scan or your government issued ID, email addresses and phone numbers, etc.

#### Log Files

Like many other web sites, xCoins's web site makes use of log files. These files merely log visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services's analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

Our web site uses cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. The cookies we may use could be both session ID cookies, which expire when you close your browser, or persistent cookies, which may remain on your hard drive for a period of time. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at your browser's web site.

#### Other Third Party Service Providers

From time to time, xCoins may use services provided by third-parties to enhance the user experience for its web sites, improve the performance of its web site, to understand more about its site visitors, or to otherwise assist xCoins in improving or making decisions about its marketing and business operations. One such service that xCoins currently uses is Google Analytics. These third-party service providers may also collect information from your browser, and may use cookies, web beacons, or other mechanisms to do so.

### HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR NON-PUBLIC INFORMATION

We will use and share any information that we collect from or about you in accordance with the Consumer Privacy Notice (which provides choices in the use and sharing of information) and any opt-in or opt-out rights that you elect to exercise. We use a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of any non-public information you may send to us or enter on our website.

#### Personal Financial Information

Any personal financial information you share with us (e.g., social security numbers, financial information, credit card numbers) will be saved, if at all, on a secured website and/or server. This information will only be available to our employees and affiliates, persons or entities providing services in connection with your loan that have a need to know the information, entities that may acquire or service your loan, or our attorneys, accountants and auditors, all of whom agree to and are bound to keep your information secure and confidential. We may also provide your personal financial information to government agencies to fulfill legal, reporting and regulatory requirements, or in response to government authorized requests for information (like subpoenas or civil investigative demands).

#### Other Non-Public Information

We may share some of the non-public information we collect about you with third parties, like companies performing services on our behalf, so long as those parties agree to keep your information confidential. We may also release your non-public information when we believe the release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

### CONSENT

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email.
